#### **Yastrebov Andrey**

<u>me@ayastrebov.com</u> Skype: <u>yastrebov3</u>

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ayastrebov

Github: github.com/Ayastrebov

Facebook: <u>facebook.com/AndrewYastrebov</u>

#### <u>Summary</u>

iOS app developer (including iPhone, iPad, iPod Touch) with five year experience in mobile application design and development. Used to develop both, mobile games and apps with complex business-logic. My goal is to create mobile software with high-performance and easily maintainable codebase on top of clean and useable UI. I am constantly learning new technologies and always try to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry. I've also contributed in some open-source projects, and stay in touch with other interesting community projects.

### **Technical Skills**

Languages: Objective-C; Java; Ruby; Python; Lua

**Development Software:** Xcode; Eclipse; AppCode IntelliJ IDEA; Netbeans;

Sublime text; PyCharm; RubyMine; Atom; Git; Svn

**Technologies:** RESTfull web services; JSON; XML; iOS Core Services;

Cocos2D; CoreData; RestKit; AFNetworking; PromiseKit; Corona;

Cocoapods; OAuth; Facebook API; Twitter API; VK API; Odnoklassniki

API

Platforms: OS X; Linux; iOS; Android

Cloud Services: Parse; Heroku; Github; Urban Airship

# **Work Experience**

Luxoft as Lead iOS developer since June 2015 to present time

1. Tinkoff iOS mobile bank apps

**Agile Fusion Corporation** as a iOS Software Engineer since July 2012 to June 2015 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Shelvz iOS app for redeeming coupons in various US stores
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Social networks integration
- 2. Jack and Jill iOS game for kids, made with corona SDK
  - Levels implementation
- 3. Fleapop iOS app. Mobile Flea market shopping
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Social networks integration
- 4. Regivit iOS shopping app, similar to eBay
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Social networks integration
- 5. <u>ThatInbox</u> iOS mail app, which utilizes mailcore2 library and INK frameworks
  - bugfixes
- 6. Mobile Appointments iOS app which integrates with build-in calendar app
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Core Data implementation
- 7. Active Learning iOS app for reading, browsing and purchasing epub books
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Core Data implementation
- 8. <u>Chefs Feed</u> iOS app, the first and only chef-powered restaurant guide.
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Social networks integration
  - Push notifications implementation
  - Bugfixes
- 9. Athens Educational iPad app for <u>University of Phoenix</u>
  - UI implementation

**FoodMap LLC** as a iOS and Android Software Engineer since May 2011 to June 2012 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1.Menutka iOS and Android app for spotting nearest cafes and restaurants and provides a full menu with a social integration.
  - UI implementation
  - API client implementation
  - Social networks integration

**Lanit-Tercom** as a iOS Software Engineer since September 2010 to May 2011 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Hunting pro iOS app for patterning a shotgun
- 2. Cafes Network iOS app (branded) for cafes. Allowing people to get new friendships in the particular cafe.
- 3. Recorder app iOS voice recording app with speex codec support

**Independent & Contract** iOS Development since January 2009 to September 2010 (Saint-Petersburg, Russia)

- 1. Various casual games, made with Cocos2D framework
- 2. Multiple iOS utility apps (one of them was top-3 Russian AppStore)
- 3. Freelance projects

## **Education**

Saint-Petersburg State University Mathematics and Mechanics Faculty Specialist degree since 2006 to 2012